[{"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804073", "answer": "\ufeffOk, in Ordnung", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uad1c\ucc2e\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804113", "answer": "w\u00fctend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ud654\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804125", "answer": "ver\u00e4rgert, w\u00fctend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9dc\uc99d\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804135", "answer": "schlecht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ub098\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804144", "answer": "sch\u00f6n", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc544\ub984\ub2f5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804153", "answer": "gro\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ud06c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804162", "answer": "bitter", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc4f0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804171", "answer": "langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2ec\uc2ec\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804180", "answer": "langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9c0\ub8e8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804189", "answer": "mutig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc529\uc529\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804198", "answer": "billig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2f8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804206", "answer": "k\u00fchl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2f8\ub298\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804215", "answer": "mollig, dick", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud1b5\ud1b5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804223", "answer": "sauber", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uae68\ub057\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804232", "answer": "wolkig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud750\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804241", "answer": "kalt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ucda5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804250", "answer": "kalt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ucc28\uac11\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804259", "answer": "angenehm, bequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804267", "answer": "praktisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud3b8\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804276", "answer": "erfrischend, k\u00fchl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\uc6d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804285", "answer": "s\u00fc\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uadc0\uc5fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804293", "answer": "nass, feucht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ucd95\ucd95\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804302", "answer": "schw\u00fcl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2b5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804311", "answer": "lecker", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9db\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804323", "answer": "anders", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2e4\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804333", "answer": "schwierig, schwer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc5b4\ub835\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804342", "answer": "dreckig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub354\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804350", "answer": "trocken", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uac74\uc870\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804358", "answer": "fr\u00fch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc774\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804367", "answer": "leicht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc27d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804375", "answer": "peinlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2f9\ud669\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804384", "answer": "leer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc5b4 \uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804393", "answer": "teuer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc2f8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804401", "answer": "schnell", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube60\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804411", "answer": "dick", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ub6b1\ub6b1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804421", "answer": "fettig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uae30\ub984\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804429", "answer": "wenig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc801\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804438", "answer": "frisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2e0\uc120\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804448", "answer": "voll", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uac00\ub4dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804457", "answer": "nass", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc816\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804466", "answer": "gl\u00fccklich, fr\u00f6hlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uae30\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804475", "answer": "gut aussehend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uc798\uc0dd\uae30\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804483", "answer": "nett", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ucc29\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804494", "answer": "gut", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uc88b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804502", "answer": "gl\u00fccklich, fr\u00f6hlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ud589\ubcf5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804511", "answer": "steif, hart", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub531\ub531\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804520", "answer": "gesund", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uac74\uac15\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804528", "answer": "hoch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub192\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804537", "answer": "hei\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub728\uac81\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804545", "answer": "hei\u00df, warm", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub365\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804557", "answer": "hungrig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubc30\uac00 \uace0\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804566", "answer": "unangenehm, unbequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd88\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804578", "answer": "interessant", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc7ac\ubbf8\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804587", "answer": "kompliziert", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubcf5\uc7a1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804595", "answer": "sp\u00e4t", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2a6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804606", "answer": "wenig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc801\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804615", "answer": "viel", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9ce\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804623", "answer": "laut", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\ub044\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804632", "answer": "gemein", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc5f4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804641", "answer": "feucht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ucd09\ucd09\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804650", "answer": "eng", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc881\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804658", "answer": "neu", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc0c8\ub86d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804669", "answer": "uninteressant, langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc7ac\ubbf8\uc5c6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804678", "answer": "nicht lecker, geschmacklos", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9db\uc5c6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804687", "answer": "alt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc624\ub798\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804695", "answer": "sch\u00f6n, h\u00fcbsch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc608\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804706", "answer": "leise", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc870\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804715", "answer": "traurig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2ac\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804723", "answer": "salzig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804731", "answer": "unheimlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\ubb34\uc12d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804740", "answer": "scharf, spitz", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub0a0\uce74\ub86d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804748", "answer": "sch\u00fcchtern", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc218\uc90d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804760", "answer": "krank, schmerzhaf", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc544\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804768", "answer": "\u00e4hnlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc2b7\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804777", "answer": "d\u00fcnn, d\u00fcrr", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uae61\ub9c8\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804786", "answer": "m\u00fcde, schl\u00e4frig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc878\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804794", "answer": "schlank", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub0a0\uc52c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804803", "answer": "rutschig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ubbf8\ub044\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804811", "answer": "langsam", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub290\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804819", "answer": "klein", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc791\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804831", "answer": "klug, smart", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub611\ub611\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804842", "answer": "weich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd80\ub4dc\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804851", "answer": "weich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9d0\ub791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804859", "answer": "sauer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804867", "answer": "scharf", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9f5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804876", "answer": "stark", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uac15\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804886", "answer": "dumm, d\u00e4mlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uba4d\uccad\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804895", "answer": "\u00fcberrascht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub180\ub77c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804904", "answer": "s\u00fc\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2ec\ub2e4, \ub2ec\ucf64\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804912", "answer": "gleich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uac19\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804923", "answer": "durstig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubaa9\uc774 \ub9c8\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804932", "answer": "m\u00fcde", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ud53c\uace4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804940", "answer": "h\u00e4\u00dflig, nicht sch\u00f6n", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubabb\uc0dd\uae30\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804949", "answer": "unangenehm, unbequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd88\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804961", "answer": "eilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uae09\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804970", "answer": "warm", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ub530\ub73b\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804979", "answer": "schwach", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uc57d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804987", "answer": "komisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uc774\uc0c1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.804996", "answer": "weit, breit", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ub113\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:11.805004", "answer": "satt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubc30\ubd80\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}]